All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
The first stop on Luffy's journey is Fishman Island, thousands of feet below sea level, where his crew becomes involved in a civil war.
After meeting with Jinbei in the sea forest, they learn of the island's hero, Fisher Tiger, who freed the slaves from Rijoire and formed the Sun Pirates.
However, when he faced an untimely death, his crew was left to pick up the pieces of his dream.
The Sun Pirates split! Jinbei vs. Arlong!
That is how our captain and our hero met his end. Not in triumph, but in tragedy. It is etched into my mind. A scene that will never fade.
Tiger's death. I believe you all know how painful it was for us. Suddenly, we were a crew without a captain. We felt so lost, and then we began to splinter apart.
Arlong! Please stay back!
Don't hurt any humans! What a load of crap! See what happens to us when we show them mercy! Get off of me!
Brother Ty! He was a damn fool!
You're wrong!
Wait! No! Arlong!
Sorry, Tiger, but you're wrong. I'll never forgive them!
All right, you punks! Get ready to die!
A fish man? He must be from...
He's awful noisy, isn't he?
A fish man?
Arlong, was it?
So what brings you here?
You wanna start trouble that bad?
Not too smart, if you ask me.
Out of my way!
Out of my way! I'm going after all the lousy humans who betrayed my captain! And you, Navy scum, can't stop me!
Oh, so this is about revenge.
Damn straight! You killed Fisher Tiger! I don't care what happens to me, but you deserve to die!
Oh, so your friend is dead. I see.
Well, you can cry if you like, but either way, you're coming with me now.
Arlong was enraged by Brother Tiger's death.
He took his anger out on humans and was imprisoned as a result.
There his hatred grew.
If he had a transfusion, he'd be fine!
Instead, he had to die, because they refused to treat fish men!
He brought that little girl back to her family, and you repaid that by killing him!
Fisher Tiger, Captain of the Sun Pirates, dies after being denied a transfusion of human blood.
Not quite, though it is close.
Regardless, the captain's dead, and humans played a big role!
Arlong lied to them. Why would he do such a thing?
Good for him. The truth is a lot worse.
Tiger chose to save that girl despite his own prejudice.
Yet humans still betrayed him, so he coldly refused to accept their blood.
On top of that, he was a slave.
If any of this became public, they would have attacked Tiger's character.
So let Arlong tell his little white lies.
You! Hey, Captain Jinbei! Enemy ship ahead!
The boss may not be with us, but we still have to keep moving forward.
Prepare yourselves! Follow Tiger's wishes and do not kill anyone!
Yeah!
From that day forward, I bore the title First Son of the Sea, and fought to do my best as Captain of the Sun Pirates.
Though in truth, fighting seemed to be the only thing our crew was doing.
I am writing this because I thought that the two of you deserved to know the whole truth about what happened.
Signed, Jinbei, Captain of the Sun Pirates.
My mind's made up.
In the end, Fisher Tiger lived the only way that he knew how.
Poor soul. I finally understand the pain that he felt that day.
As their leader, I must remain strong. I won't give in.
We two shall live under the sun, and try to understand one another. If I may, signing here is the first step to harmony.
With all due respect, Queen Odohime, you must be out of your mind!
Fisher Tiger freed countless slaves, both fishmen and human. He didn't care about what race they were.
Yet humans still refused to help him.
Who cares about understanding?
Another fruitless day without any signatures.
Mother!
My sweet children!
Hey Mother, are you okay?
Yeah, what's wrong? You look so sad!
Mother, you really need some rest.
You children brighten my day.
I'm fine, don't worry.
Okay, I won't.
If you say so, Mother!
I'll keep doing my best.
To make this world a better place for everyone.
Queen Otohime was working so hard.
Day after day.
She rescued humans from shipwrecks.
Are you alright?
Pirates must have hit them.
Please help me.
Don't worry, we're here.
Bring the wounded to the island!
She taught the island children about the world above.
Does anybody remember what this area with many trees is called?
You there.
Forest?
Like the sea forest!
And collected signatures.
Please wait!
I just need a moment of your time!
However...
Queen Otohime!
Oh!
Hello again!
Thank you for showing your support the other day.
Actually, about that.
We're curious.
How many signatures do you have?
Well, I've been collecting them for five years now.
One hundred sheets have been signed, with each containing ten signatures.
So that adds up to one thousand supporters.
Still, the population of the island is five million, so we're not done yet.
Step by step, right?
Um...
We have kind of a big favor to ask.
We'd like to withdraw our signatures.
They total about half of what you have.
Does that sound okay?
Huh?
You must not have heard about it, but...
Those human pirates that you rescued the other day?
They committed a robbery in town before escaping from the island.
Uh...
Your Majesty.
Queen Otohime!
Oh, hello, children!
Oh, hello!
Hi!
Hello, I'm your host!
Are you ready for another lesson yet?
Excuse me!
My mom looks that paper I signed the other day back!
I found it!
Yeah!
Go ahead, mommy!
May I help you?
I do hope there's no hard feelings,
what with you being the queen and all?
I just can't do it.
Humans are too evil.
evil we'll pass on the speeches to yeah sorry about all this we've just had
enough
what an exhausting day I think I might have overdone it a bit out there I'm
sorry sweeties but could you give your mother some alone time today
your majesty this is on the air everyone can hear you
why don't you shut up mister at the left
mister at the left
majesty have you been drinking mind your business got it
leave me alone I'm not drunk at all
yes you are goodness what's happening is that really queen otohime
everybody better listen to me you can live however you want if that means staying in
this island then I can't stop you neither can anyone else but in the vastness of
the ocean so broad and on the sea floor foreboding and dark
we chose this tiny place and this place alone do you have any idea why
queen otohime isn't it because this is where we can get a bit of sunlight or we can get a bit of air
luxuries down here are plentiful above ground light illuminates the entire
surface and the sky stretches out as far as you can see
our children why do they always sneak out to catch a glimpse of Saba Odie Park
huh can't you see the world is filled with more beauty than any of us can even imagine
there's no place that we shouldn't be able to go
why restrict ourselves to this bubble
I know you tell yourselves life down here is comfortable
but you're safe
do you want to spend the rest of your lives trapped
dig deep summon your courage
once you have it pursue your dreams no matter the cost
your majesty
if humans stand in your way we'll face them together
you don't have to confront your fears alone
and maybe then we can finally make a difference for the future
for our children for the island
even if it's just a small one
it's rough
it's rough I left my family behind on fish man island
my wife and kids hope they're doing okay
going home again isn't that simple not for us
we're escaped slaves and pirates to boot
so we got to put our own dreams on hold
we might be stuck sailing for the rest of our lives
I'm sorry
you know I'm sure my family's doing okay
my goodness
you've seen better days
he was formidable
I see
he certainly did a number on you
didn't he
Arlong
the fish man that we just locked up and impelled down
he was nothing
but you have to watch out for this one
Jinbei
he's quite strong
even by fish man standards
he's far too dangerous at large
we should bring him in
unbelievable
me and the seven warlords
oh it's not that surprising
you're worth 250 million
with a bounty that big
they definitely see you as a threat to the world government
that's the highest praise a pirate can get from those chumps
Mackerel's right
they're finally taking us seriously
all you need to do is reject them
that'll really help us buy along the notoriety
no one will ever mess with us
choo
my mind is made up
I'm going to take the navy's offer
what?
welcome home Jinbei
I heard about the seven warlords proposal
if I join
Aladdin and the other crew members
who do not wish to be pirates
no longer have to be
they can live in this country
without fear of retribution
it's a way for me to take care of my men
but more importantly
if I do become a warlord
it will help the fishermen become closer to the world government
we need that relationship
I can atone for all the trouble that we've caused the queen
thank you
at the moment she's
not feeling very well
in the end
we might see Tiger's dream
liberation and freedom for all fishermen
everywhere
though
then again
we'd have to watch our own
there are some less deserving of amnesty
if you have something to say to me
then you'd better speak up now
you expect to thank you
for becoming a sellout
you may have set me free
but the navy owns you
have you forgotten what brother Ty said before he died?
you mustn't let anger and bitterness overwhelm you
sounds to me like you've gotten soft
sure I'd probably be safer if I followed your lead
but there's no way in hell I'm doing that
you can't make me save
in case you forgot
Tiger is dead
which means I'm free
free to lead my own crew
now if you'll excuse me
I'll be taking back my men
got a problem with that?
you fool
you damn ignorant fool
hey now
enough with the name code
let's end this
right now
just you and me
what?
Arlong?
no!
if you don't do it
I'm free to go
fair warning
I won't go down easily
you'll have to kill me
arrogant
paw
don't do this
that's more like it
please stop it
jimay no!
no!
do whatever you want
Arlong!
I wouldn't dwell on it
there's nothing you could have done
you've known each other since childhood after all
like him or not he's still like a brother to you
and you're no killer
he's blinded by hate
he'll never understand
what Tiger meant by his dying words
it doesn't matter how far he goes
as long as Arlong engages in violence the navy will be after him
worst comes to worst
we may have to stop Arlong ourselves one day
at any cost
only time will tell
look
I'd love to stay and chat
Captain Jinbei
but we're headed out to
good luck
you're gonna need it
Macro!
come back here!
if they want to leave, let them
so long, suckers!
damn it
he's stronger than I realized
uh... you...
Archie
you can't look back
the Sun Pirates split into three groups
with Arlong
Macro
and myself as captains
and ever since then
we have continued going our separate ways
Jinbei accepts a position as a warlord of the sea
granting freedom to the fishmen who fought beside him
returning home at long last
they look forward to an era of peace
led by Queen Otohime
however
the appearance of a celestial dragon
places the future of their island
in jeopardy
on the next
One Piece
Shaking Fishman Island
a celestial dragon drifts in
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!